(Raj:)it would give you an
open floor plan,
(Raj:)and then-- it's a little scary,
but could be fun--
(Raj:)indoor fire pit.
(doorbell rings)
(Howard:)Hey, I grew up
in this house, okay?
(Howard:)No one's knocking anything down.
(Bernadette:)Okay, okay.
(Bernadette:)When he's at Comic-Con,
(Bernadette:)I'm bringing in
a wrecking ball.
(Howard(answering door):)Can I help you?
(Guy at door:)Hi. Are you Howard Wolowitz?
(Raj:)Yes.
(Guy:)Um, this is a little weird,
(Guy:)but a lawyer was trying
to contact my father,
(Guy:)because his name was still
on the title for this house.
W... uh, who's your father?
(Guy:)Sam Wolowitz.
(chuckles)
S-Sam Wolowitz is my father.
(Guy:)I know.
(Howard:)Well, wait, so if we have
the same father...
I mean,
(Howard:)are you saying
(Howard:)you're my half-brother?
(Guy:)I think so.
(chuckles)
(Howard:)Bernadette, weird things
are happening out here!